<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="overdraft_quote_terms_and_conditions">1.How our Overdraft Credit Facility works.\n
Our Overdraft Credit Facility allows you to borrow money on your current account by drawing up to your Credit Limit.
If you already have an overdraft credit facility with another bank then this agreement forms a conditional offer and your credit facility will become available to you once you have deposited at least 70 (seventy) per cent of your income into your account. If you do not do this within 90 (ninety) days from the date that you accept this agreement, the overdraft facility will no longer be available to you.\n\n
2.Quotation and Agreement.\n
This Quotation and Agreement:\n
\t• sets out our terms;\n
\t• is open for you to accept for 5 (five) business days; and\n
\t• is the agreement between us if you accept.\n
In the rest of these terms we refer to:\n
\t• this Quotation and Agreement as this ‘Agreement’;\n
\t• your Overdraft Credit Facility as your ‘Credit Facility’;\n
\t• your current account with us as your ‘Account’; and\n
\t• a debit balance on your Account as your ‘Balance’.\n
This Agreement is to be read with the Personal Client Agreement, which contains important terms and information about credit under the NCA.\n\n
3.Interest, fees, and costs\n
You agree to pay the interest, fees and costs referred to in this Agreement and the Personal Client Agreement which we will debit to your Account monthly in arrears. We will debit the initiation fee to your account when we grant your overdraft facility.\n\n
4.Charging interest\n
We charge interest on your Balance as at midnight each day.\n\n
5.Interest rates\n
The Discounted Annual Interest Rate applies provided your Balance does not exceed your Credit Limit.
The Contractual Annual Interest Rate applies to that part of your Balance that exceeds your Credit Limit and/or when you are in default under this Agreement.
The interest rates are variable being at a percentage margin above or below our ‘Reference rate’.
Our Reference rate is our published base annual interest rate for lending, which varies from time to time and is also known as our ‘Prime’ rate. Within 30 (thirty) business days after a change in our reference rate, we will notify you in writing of the change and the new interest rates.\n\n
6.Fees\n
The monthly OD ledger fee applies for each month in which you have your Credit Facility.
We can change our fees by notifying you in writing at least 5 (five) business days before the change takes effect.\n\n
7.Security\n
If it is a condition of your Credit Facility that you provide security, it must be in place before you can draw on your Credit Limit.\n\n
8.Funding your Account\n
We may require you to pay enough money into your Account by a due date to:\n
\t• pay 1 (one) or more month’s interest and fees; and\n
\t• ensure your Balance does not exceed your Credit Limit.\n\n
9.Increasing your Credit Limit\n
We may increase your Credit Limit:\n
\t• by agreement with you, subject to us first carrying out a fresh assessment of your ability to repay your Credit Facility with the increased Credit Limit; or\n
\t• on a temporary basis; or\n
\t• automatically, if you take the option of an automatic annual Credit Limit increase when you applied for your Credit Facility or take up this option later.\n\n
10.Temporary increase of your Credit Limit\n
We may allow your Balance to exceed your Credit Limit temporarily to accommodate payment transactions on your Account. You must reduce your Balance within your Credit Limit within 30 (thirty) days after the date of the first transaction that causes your Balance to exceed your Credit Limit.
If we allow you a temporary increase you agree that the:
Contractual Annual Interest Rate will apply to the part of your Balance that exceeds your Credit Limit.\n\n
11.Decreasing your Credit Limit\n
You may decrease your Credit Limit at any time by notifying us in writing, the decrease taking effect within 30 (thirty) business days after we received your notification.
We may decrease your Credit Limit at any time by notifying you in writing, the decrease taking effect on delivery of our notification.
When we decrease your Credit Limit, you agree to reduce your Balance within your new reduced Credit Limit within 30 (thirty) business days after delivery of the notification decreasing your Credit Limit.\n\n
12.Changing the day upon which we debit fees and interest to your Account\n
We may change the day in the month when we debit interest and fees to your Account. We will notify you at least 5 (five) business days before the date upon which the debit will occur.\n\n
13.Suspending your Credit Facility\n
We may suspend your Credit Facility at any time by notifying you in writing, the suspension taking effect on delivery of the notification. While your Credit Facility is suspended you cannot draw on your Credit Limit.\n\n
14.Ending your Credit Facility\n
Your Credit Facility will continue until we or you bring it to an end.
You can end your Credit Facility by repaying your Balance together with interest and fees accrued up to the date of payment but not yet charged to your Account, (we will provide this information to you) and notifying us that you no longer require your Credit Facility.
We can end your Credit Facility by notifying you in writing:\n
\t• suspending your Credit Facility immediately, the suspension taking effect on delivery of the notification, and requiring you to repay your Balance within 10 (ten) business days, or as otherwise agreed, after the delivery of the notification,together with any interest and fees accrued up to the date of payment but not yet debited to your Account.\n\n
15.Default\n
You will be in default under the terms of this Agreement if any of the following occur:\n
\t• you do not comply with your obligations under the Personal Client Agreement;\n
\t• your Balance exceeds your Credit Limit unless the excess is in accordance with a temporary increase that we have allowed; or\n
\t• you do not reduce your Balance within your Credit Limit within 30 (thirty) days after the date of the first transaction that causes your Balance to exceed your Credit Limit;\n
\t• you do not reduce your Balance within your new reduced Credit Limit within 30 (thirty) business days after delivery of the notice reducing your credit limit; or\n
\t• on the expiration of 10 (ten) business days, or as otherwise agreed, after we have delivered a notice ending your Credit Facility you have not repaid your Balance including any interest, fees and costs, accrued but not debited to your Account.\n\n
16.Consequences of Default\n
Please refer to the consequences of default set out in the Personal Client Agreement.
</string>
    <string name="overdraft_quote_terms_and_conditions_credit_protection">
Credit Protection Plan\n\n
Underwriter Details\n
This Credit Life is underwritten by Absa Life Limited (“Absa Life”) a licensed long term insurer.\n
Optional / Condition of Lending\n
This Credit Life is optional.\n
Eligibility for Credit Life\n
To be eligible for the Credit Life Protection Insurance Cover (‘Credit Life’), you, the Life Insured, must meet the following conditions:\n
	\t•	You must have an Overdraft Facility with Absa Bank; and\n
	\t•	You must be at least 18 years of age and not older than 64 years of age. Note exclusions and limitations to benefits.\n
Minimum and Maximum Sum Insured
The Credit Life Sum Insured is equal to the Credit Limit on your Overdraft Facility, rounded up to the nearest R1 000,00, subject to a minimum amount of R10 000,00 and a maximum amount of R150 000,00.\n
Cover Start date\n
The ‘cover start date’ is the date on which the credit agreement, for which the Credit Life is taken, becomes effective.\n
Description of Credit Life Benefits and Limitations\n
	\t•	In the event of your Death or Permanent Disability, and subject to all other Credit Life conditions being met, Absa Life will pay the Credit Limit on your Overdraft Facility, up to the maximum sum insured.\n
	\t•	In the event of you being diagnosed with any one of the following medical conditions (also known as Dread Disease) *, and subject to all other Credit Life conditions being met, Absa Life will pay the Credit Limit on your Overdraft Facility, up to the maximum sum insured:\n
Heart attack Stroke\n
Cancer\n
Melanoma is included but melanoma-in-situ is excluded\n
Renal failure\n
Paraplegia\n
Blindness\n
Surgery for coronary heart disease\n
Surgery for a disease of the aorta\n
Replacement of a heart valve\n
Organ transplant\n
Coma\n
Major burns\n
Loss of limb\n
Loss of speech\n
HIV through blood transfusion\n
*The full detail of each of these Dread Disease events is contained in the Credit Life Policy Terms and Conditions.\n
	\t•	In the event of your Temporary Disability, and subject to all other Credit Life conditions being met, Absa Life will pay a monthly amount of 3% of the sum insured into your Overdraft Facility account, for a maximum period of 12 months. Temporary Disability will be payable after you have been temporarily disabled for a period of 30 days.\n
	\t•	In the event of your Retrenchment, and subject to all other Credit Life conditions being met, Absa Life will pay a monthly amount of 3% of the sum insured into your Overdraft Facility account, for a maximum period of 12 months. The Retrenchment benefit is subject to a 3 month waiting period, from the cover start date or date of previous claim.\n
Term of Credit Life Cover\n
Credit Life cover extends over the following terms:\n
	\t•	In the event of your Death, and subject to all other Credit Life conditions being met, the term of cover will be up to 65 years of age;\n
	\t•	In the event of your Permanent or Temporary Disability, and subject to all other Credit Life conditions being met, the term of cover will be up to 65 years of age;\n
	\t•	In the event of you being diagnosed with any one of the Dread Diseases listed above, and subject to all other Credit Life conditions being met, the term of cover will be up to 60 years of age; and\n
	\t•	In the event of your Retrenchment, and subject to all other Credit Life conditions being met, the term of cover will be up to 60 years of age.\n
Credit Life Exclusions acknowledged by you\n
Absa Life will not pay a benefit if your Death or Permanent Disability or Temporary Disability or Dread Disease was caused by any one of the following events (including but not limited to):\n
	\t•	If you received medical treatment for a particular injury, illness or condition in the previous 12 months before the cover start date, you shall not be covered for that injury or illness or condition for the first 12 months after the cover start date; or\n
	\t•	If you refuse any reasonable recommendation for medical treatment, either by your own medical practitioner or by Absa Life, you shall not be covered for any related claim; or\n
	\t•	The abuse of alcohol, drugs or narcotics; or\n
	\t•	Wilful self-inflicted injury or suicide, within 2 years of the cover start date or any reinstatement date; or\n
	\t•	Active participation in war, invasion, acts of foreign enemies, hostilities, warlike operations (whether war be declared or not), civil war, insurrection, rebellion revolution, civil commotion or uprisings, military power; or\n
	\t•	The use of nuclear, biological or chemical weapons or any radioactive contamination; or\n
	\t•	Participation in criminal activities; or\n
	\t•	Participation in hazardous activities such as mountain climbing, bungee jumping and speed racing.\n
Absa Life will not pay a retrenchment benefit claim that results from:\n
	\t•	Lawful dismissal, including dismissal as a result of wilful conduct that is a violation of some established, definite rule of conduct, a forbidden act, wilful dereliction of duty or misconduct; or\n
	\t•	Voluntary forfeiture of salary, wages or other employment income; or\n
	\t•	Voluntary retrenchment or termination of employment; or\n
	\t•	Resignation; or\n
	\t•	Retirement; or\n
	\t•	Participation in an unprotected strike; or\n
	\t•	Retrenchment of which you were aware or received notice of during the 3 months preceding the cover start date; or\n
	\t•	You being: employed on a contract basis; self-employed and/or employed in a business owned by your family or where you are a decision-maker; or\n
	\t•	You being employed by your current employer for a period of less than 6 months prior to the Retrenchment date.\n
When will there be a changes in your Credit Life premium\n
Absa Life may change your Credit Life premium at any time if the conditions of policies similar to yours change from what Absa Life expected at the cover start date.
If Absa Life changes your Credit Life premium, you will be notified of such change at least 90 days before the change takes effect.\n
When will this Credit Life lapse
Credit Life will lapse when you do not pay an outstanding premium even after you have been given notice to pay (‘Grace Period’) and that Grace Period has expired.  This means that you will no longer have Credit Life cover with Absa Life.\n
Cooling Off Period\n
You have 31 days from the cover start date to cancel this Credit Life, with no obligations. If you cancel this Credit Life within the Cooling Off Period, Absa Life will refund any amounts that you have already paid, on condition that no benefit has been paid out to you.\n
When may you cancel this Credit life\n
You have the right to cancel this Credit Life at any time by notifying Absa Life. If you cancel the Credit Life after the Cooling Off Period, Absa Life will not refund any premiums paid.\n\n
How to lodge a Claim\n
In the event of a claim, the nearest branch should be the first point of contact. Alternatively, please contact Absa Life.\n
Tel:  0860 227 253\n
Absa Life Claims department\n
Email: creditlifeclaims@absa.co.za\n
Fax: 011 223 1643\n
Contact Details for queries and complaints\n
General Enquiries\n
Tel: 0860 227 253\n\n
If your query has not been resolved or you are not satisfied with a decision made regarding your claim, you can send your complaint in writing to the Complaints Resolution Committee.\n
Email: absalifecrc@absa.co.za\n
PO Box 421\n
Johannesburg\n
2000\n\n
The Ombudsman for Long-term Insurance\n
If you wish to complain about this insurance product, its terms or the way that the product is administered, please contact the Ombudsman for Long-term Insurance.\n
Ombudsman for Long-term Insurance\n
Private Bag X45\n
Claremont\n
7735\n
Tel: 021 657 5000/0860 103 236\n
Fax: 021 674 0951\n
Email: info@ombud.co.za\n
Website: www.ombud.co.za\n\n
The Ombudsman for (FAIS)\n
If you wish to complain about the way this policy was sold to you, please contact The Ombudsman for Financial Advisory and Intermediary Services (FAIS):\n
The Ombudsman for FAIS\n
PO Box 74571\n
Lynnwood Ridge\n
0040</string>
</resources>